Batwo AI Marketing - business_management Permission Demo
바투 AI 마케팅 - business_management 권한 데모
This permission allows users to manage business assets like Meta Pixels.
이 권한으로 비즈니스 자산(픽셀)을 관리합니다.
Click the Settings menu.
설정 메뉴를 클릭합니다.
Select "Pixel Installation" from the Settings menu.
설정 페이지의 메뉴에서 "픽셀 설치"를 선택합니다.
The Pixel Management page is displayed.
픽셀 관리 페이지가 표시됩니다.
API call: GET /me/businesses
API 호출: GET /me/businesses
User's business accounts are loaded.
사용자의 비즈니스 계정이 로드됩니다.
API call: GET //adspixels
API 호출: GET //adspixels
List of connected Meta Pixels is displayed.
연결된 Meta 픽셀 목록이 표시됩니다.
Pixel 1: "Main Store Pixel" - Pixel ID: 123456789 - Status: Active - Connected Website: www.mystore.com
픽셀 1: "Main Store Pixel" - Pixel ID: 123456789 - 상태: 활성 - 연결된 웹사이트: www.mystore.com
Pixel 2: "Mobile App Pixel" - Pixel ID: 987654321 - Status: Active - Event Match Rate: 85%
픽셀 2: "Mobile App Pixel" - Pixel ID: 987654321 - 상태: 활성 - 이벤트 매칭 비율: 85%
Click "Main Store Pixel" to view detailed information.
"Main Store Pixel"을 클릭하여 상세 정보를 확인합니다.
Pixel detail page is displayed.
픽셀 상세 페이지가 표시됩니다.
Pixel Name: "Main Store Pixel"
픽셀 이름: "Main Store Pixel"
Pixel ID: 123456789
Pixel ID: 123456789
Installation Status: Verified
설치 상태: 확인됨
Tracked Events: - PageView: 1,245,678 - ViewContent: 456,789 - AddToCart: 123,456 - Purchase: 45,678
추적 이벤트: - PageView: 1,245,678 - ViewContent: 456,789 - AddToCart: 123,456 - Purchase: 45,678
Click the "Copy Installation Code" button.
"설치 코드 복사" 버튼을 클릭합니다.
Pixel installation code is copied to clipboard.
클립보드에 픽셀 설치 코드가 복사됩니다.
Meta Pixel Installation Code: ...
Meta 픽셀 설치 코드: ...
Users paste this code into their website.
사용자는 이 코드를 자신의 웹사이트에 붙여넣습니다.
Once installed, the pixel automatically starts tracking visitors.
픽셀이 웹사이트에 설치되면 자동으로 방문자 추적을 시작합니다.
Click the "Create New Pixel" button.
"새 픽셀 생성" 버튼을 클릭합니다.
New pixel creation form is displayed.
새 픽셀 생성 폼이 표시됩니다.
Enter pixel name: "New Campaign Pixel"
픽셀 이름을 입력합니다: "New Campaign Pixel"
Pixel description: "Tracking for new product campaign"
픽셀 설명: "Tracking for new product campaign"
Click the "Create" button.
"생성" 버튼을 클릭합니다.
API call: POST //adspixels
API 호출: POST //adspixels
New pixel has been successfully created.
새 픽셀이 성공적으로 생성되었습니다.
New Pixel ID: 111222333
새 픽셀 ID: 111222333
Return to pixel list.
픽셀 목록으로 돌아갑니다.
The newly created "New Campaign Pixel" is added to the list.
새로 생성된 "New Campaign Pixel"이 목록에 추가되었습니다.
With business_management permission, you can:
business_management 권한으로 다음을 수행할 수 있습니다:
- View pixels in business accounts - Check pixel details - Create new pixels - Get pixel installation code - Monitor event match rates
- 비즈니스 계정의 픽셀 목록 조회 - 픽셀 상세 정보 확인 - 새 픽셀 생성 - 픽셀 설치 코드 조회 - 이벤트 매칭 비율 모니터링
E-commerce merchants can manage all pixels from our app.
e-커머스 사업자는 우리 앱에서 한 번에 모든 픽셀을 관리합니다.
No need to access Meta Ads Manager separately.
Meta Ads Manager에 따로 접속할 필요가 없습니다.
Pixels enable visitor tracking and conversion measurement.
픽셀을 통해 방문자 추적과 전환 측정이 가능해집니다.
business_management permission demo completed.
business_management 권한 데모를 완료했습니다.